<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Tom Yeoman]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tom Yeoman personal site. Contains my personal blog and projects]]></description><link>https://tomyeoman.me</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 10:22:56 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[Goals 2021]]></title><description><![CDATA[Recap This year has been tough. Living in the UK and faced with lockdown for most of the year, my goals shifted a lot from taking on the…]]></description><link>https://tomyeoman.me/goals-2021/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://tomyeoman.me/goals-2021/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h3&gt;Recap&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This year has been tough. Living in the UK and faced with lockdown for most of the year, my goals shifted a lot from taking on the world, to staying sane!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At a retrospective - it’s fair to say In the past I have been over ambitious with my goal selection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have tried the extreme, listing every area in my life, setting goals, then projects against them etc. Whilst I do believe this promotes a well balanced life and I really like the idea on paper - for me it becomes an operation burdon, and a drain on my energy juggling goals in every area, continuously.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This year I want to rely on habits more, reducing required motivation to achieve a lot more, getting “free” productivity in certain areas. E.G daily medititation / journaling&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Outside my my habits, whilst i’ll stick with goals - I prefer not to always rely on well defined projects projects and tasks (although they certainly have a place). Instead focus on a daily highlight, that makes my day “worth it”.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Habits&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In order to improve habits stickyness, and not overwhelm myself trying to tackle everything, every day, i’ll be setting days for partiicular activities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gym 3x a week, running 2x&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Piano practice twice per week (monday, thursday)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Side project twice per week (tuesday, friday / weekend)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Daily “Learn something new” for 1 hour in the morning before work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Complete my daily&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These will all be tracked using beeminder, with public links available here -&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Goals&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Run a 5k in 25 minutes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Move away from England (could be another difficult year for this - lets see how this one goes)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Play a full song on piano&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create and release a song&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build &amp;#x26; release my first online game (“io” style)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build &amp;#x26; release my first SAAS product&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are a few career / personal goals i’ve kept from the list, with the above being those i’m happy being public for now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Have a good new year all, thanks for reading.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>